All right, I want to do a quick demonstration
for what I think is the best setup for the
Work Louder Creator Micro 2.
For me, I use the Claude Desktop and ChatGPT
desktop apps all the time.
I use it for coding.
I often switch between Claude Chat, Claude Code,
ChatGPT, and Codex all the time every day.
And if you want a hands-off experience,
you can use this.
I created a helper app that you can download
off of my GitHub, completely free, that allows
you to quickly do things like change to Chat,
Codex, ChatGPT, and back to Claude Code.
It is really flexible, easy, gives you a whole set of,
I think, the best set of keys that's
out there for working completely hands-free,
everything from approval, denial, changing
the model, doing dictation, submission, new line.
The joystick gives you access to select all,
paste, tab, and a standard copy.
You can also click the dial to search past chats,
create new chats, and stop activity.
This works the same across
all four different form factors.
Makes it really flexible and easy to use.